{
    "id": "04df77a802644a81881932bf5f31224d",
    "title": "Modal Auxiliary Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "It is not necessary for you to wait any longer. / You ..................... not wait any longer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "need",
                "should",
                "must"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "33a1849f3a3b4601b0b067ddca7cb386"
        },
        {
            "question": "You are required to respect the national flag. / You ........................ respect the national flag.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "would",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "994491780e0049dab8b3e4649bc5f8a9"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was able to read when she was three. / She .................. write when she was three.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "could",
                "might"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "52d495605d424473b15f5bb4b071f678"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was able to solve the problem. / I ................................. solve the problem.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4edba95246c84b5d9b6fcdc562aca8e0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Perhaps she would come. / She ......................... come.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should",
                "might"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2f089c0af91c42b2b1f5aa4bd9a1767c"
        },
        {
            "question": "You are prohibited from entering my home. / You ....................... enter my house.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "must",
                "must not",
                "need not"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d0e3fc9bf46941d6994bd3e78883f9aa"
        },
        {
            "question": "You are allowed to go home. / You ..................... go home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "may",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "aac37dce90854110a7eccb4532805ab7"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is able to speak English. / She ....................... speak English.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "may",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "35eb2710ce714a0eaf0823255ac67b9d"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is possible to blow glass. / Glass ......................... be blown.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "may",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e8a6d67fe0d547a88501bdab493fd8b5"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is not necessary for her to pay for that call. / She .................... pay for that call.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "needs not",
                "need not",
                "may not"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "01d5a6be1c134794bbb63ee798f96e40"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is possible for wars to break out at any time. / Wars .......................... break out at any time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "may",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b32d5ab08280404f9888d66b20a8f085"
        },
        {
            "question": "I prefer to stay at home instead of going to the club. / I .......................... rather stay at home than go to the club.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "could",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "842b858a8b3a45eda7b35e5fc69bd06a"
        }
    ]
}